#### Contactar

winninglero@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ jorgealvarezore (LinkedIn) jorgealvarezore.github.io (Personal)

# Aptitudes principales

Diseño asistido por ordenador (CAD) Análisis de datos AutoCAD Civil 3D

# Languages

Inglés (Professional Working)
Francés (Limited Working)
Español (Native or Bilingual)

## Certifications

Curso de Principios de Visualización de Datos para Business Intelligence

Curso de Fundamentos de .NET

Taller de Inglés Básico A1 para Principiantes

Curso de Fundamentos de Álgebra Lineal con Python

Data Science e Inteligencia Artificial

#### Honors-Awards

Beca 1er lugar del ciclo Topografía III

# Jorge Alvarez

Data analyst | Data scientist | GIS/CAD | Environmental/Mining engineer | Interested in Machine Learning and Artificial Intelligence Perú

## Extracto

I am a passionate student of Data Analyst and Data Scientist at Platzi. My previous work experience was in Environmental Engineering specifically in GIS and CAD desing on ArcGIS and AutoCAD softwares. Technician degree in Surveyor at SENCICO, Bachelor's degree in Environmental Engineering at UNFV, Graduated in Master Degree in Mining and Environmental Management at UNMSM.

# Experiencia

#### Autónomo

Geographic Information System Specialist enero de 2022 - Present (1 año)

Lima, Perú

Design and draw thematic maps for environment projects

JCI Ingeniería & Servicios Ambientales Geographic Information System Specialist febrero de 2018 - diciembre de 2021 (3 años 11 meses) Miraflores, Lima, Perú

Design and draw thematic maps for environment projects. Constantly update the internal geographic database with latest official GIS info.

## OHL

Computer Aided Design Specialist octubre de 2012 - abril de 2013 (7 meses)

Challhuahuacho, Apurímac, Perú

Draw, design and doing some calculations in AutoCAD Civil 3D

Doris Flores Computer Aided Design Specialist 2011 - 2012 (1 año) Lima, Perú Draw architectural plans

# Educación

#### Platzi

Data analyst, Tecnología de la información · (diciembre de 2021)

# Universidad Nacional Mayor de San Marcos

Maestría, Ingeniería de minas y minerales · (marzo de 2018 - diciembre de 2019)

#### Universidad Nacional Federico Villarreal

Ingeniero ambiental, Ingenieria ambiental · (2007 - 2015)

#### Sencico

Técnico topógrafo, Topografía y cartografía · (julio de 2009 - diciembre de 2011)